UNITE Local 23-25 Publications 6000/024 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NY Metro Area Joint Board News Vol. No. 1 (2004; Spring/Summer) Chinese, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 2: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 3: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
- NY Metro Area Joint Board News. V. 2; No. 1 (2005:Jan.), Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board News, 2005; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (2005:Jan.)
- The Magnet. No. 2 (2000: Summer) English and Spanish, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: The Magnet: Drawing Workers Together, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Author: New York Apparel and Allied Workers Joint Board
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (2000:Summer)
- Voice 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: UNITE Voice, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Author: Knitgoods Workers' Union, Local 155
    Notes: v.61:no.1 (2002:Winter)
  - Item 2: UNITE Voice, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Notes: v.62:no.3 (2003:Fall)
- The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride at a Glance, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Author: The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride
    Language: English; Spanish;Chinese.
  - Item 2: The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride at a Glance, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Notes: Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride at a Glance, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Notes: Copy 3.
- Over 100 Years Ago, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Over 100 years ago, a group of immigrant workers got together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Over 100 years ago, a group of immigrant workers got together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 3: Over 100 years ago, a group of immigrant workers got together, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 4: Hace mas de 100 years anos, un grupo de trabajadores inmigrantes se unieron, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Language: Spanish.
- Good Chants for a Lively Picketing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Good Chants for a Lively Picketline and Some Great Songs, Too, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Author: Ruth Goldbaum; Rini Templeton
  - Item 2: Good Chants for a Lively Picketline and Some Great Songs, Too, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 3: Good Chants for a Lively Picketline and Some Great Songs, Too, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
- UNITE! Proudly Made in New York 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: UNITE! Proudly Made In New York, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Author: UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees)
    Notes: Shopping Guide: Where to Buy Made in New York Fashion
  - Item 2: UNITE! Proudly Made In New York, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Notes: Shopping Guide: Where to Buy Made in New York Fashion. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE! Proudly Made In New York, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Notes: Shopping Guide: Where to Buy Made in New York Fashion. Copy 3.
- English-Chinese, Chinese-English Needle Trades Dictionary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: English-Chinese; Chinese-English Needletrades Dictionary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Language: English;Chinese.
  - Item 2: Shop Rep's Dictionary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Notes: English-Chinese, Chinese-English dictionary of union terminology
    Language: English; Chinese.
- Working Agreement Atlantic Apparel, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Working Agreement: Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association with Pennsylvania, Ohio and South Jersey Joint Board, UNITE, 2004- 2007 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Author: Atlantic Apparel Contractors' Association; UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees)
    Notes: June 1, 2004 until May 31, 2007
- Calendars 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Calendar, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Item 2: Calendar, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Item 3: Calendar, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
- AFL-CIO Committee of the Evolution of Work 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The Future of Work, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Author: AFL-CIO Committee on the Evolution of Work
    Notes: August 1983.
  - Item 2: The Changing Situation Of Workers and Their Unions, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Notes: February 1985.
- Workers Rights Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Workers' Rights Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Author: UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees); Garment Workers' Center
    Notes: Chinese-language version on opposing pages
- Garment District Day Care Center of Chinatown 1999, Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Fundraising Reception, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Author: Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown
    Notes: September 29, 1999.
- Garment Industry Development Corp. 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Author: Garment Industry Development Corporation
- Chinatown After September 11th 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Chinatown After September 11th: An Economic Impact Study, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Author: Asian American Federation of New York
    Notes: April, 2002.
- UNITE! Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 2: Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 3: Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
- UNITE! Manual Del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Manual Del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Item 2: Manual Del Delegado Sindical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
- UNITE Constitution 1995, Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
- UNITE Constitution. Spanish 1995, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Constitucion, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Item 2: Constitucion, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
- UNITE! Constitution. Spanish English 1999, Publication (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Constitucion, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Item 2: Constitucion, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Constitution 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Constitucion, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Prescription Drug Program 2 2002, Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Prescription Drug Program II, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Author: UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees); Medco Health Solutions
    Notes: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund
  - Item 2: Prescription Drug Program II, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Notes: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Programa II de Medicamentos con Receta Medica, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Notes: Fondo Medico y de Bienestar de los Estados del Este
  - Item 4: Programa II de Medicamentos con Receta Medica, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Notes: Fondo Medico y de Bienestar de los Estados del Este. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: Prescription Drug Program, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Language: English; Spanish; Chinese.
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund 2001, Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Summary Plan Description, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Notes: Form 4-01-FR
  - Item 2: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Summary Plan Description, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Notes: Form 4-01-AE/MA/RS/ES
  - Item 3: Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Summary Plan Description, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Notes: Form 4-01-AE/MA/RS/ES. Copy 2.
- Workers Book of Rights English; Spanish 1997, Publication (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Workers Book of Rights, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Bienveninas a UNITE Compana para el Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Bienvenidos a UNITE: Trabajando por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Item 2: Campana para el Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Local 23-25 Cordially Invites You 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Local 23-25 cordially invites you to a Reception celebrating our 100th Anniversary, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 79)
- New Steps of the Union 1997, Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: New Steps of the Union, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Notes: UNITE Worker Education Program, Summer 1997
- Union Health Center Newsletter 1999, Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
    Author: Union Health Center
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1999:Spring)
- GED Report 2003, Publication (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Executive Board to the Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Item 2: Report of the General Executive Board to the Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Organize! Mobilizer! UNITE! 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Organize! Mobilize! UNITE! Report of the Proceedings of the Second Constitutional Convention, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Proposed Regulations Assigned to Committees 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Organize! Mobilize! UNITE! Proposed Resolutions Assigned to Committees, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: Second Constitutional Convention
- Composite Resolutions Passed, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Organize! Mobilize! UNITE! Composite Resolutions Passed, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- GEB Meeting June 3-4, 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: GEB Meeting, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 3-4, 2003
- GEB Meeting July 16-17, 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: GEB Meeting, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 16-17, 2003
- GEB Meeting October 20-22, 2003, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: GEB Meeting, 2003; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: October 20-22, 2003
- The Insurance representatives Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Insurance Representative's Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Amalgamated Life
- UNITE! Directory 2001, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: UNITE Directory, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: Fall/Winter 2001
- Product Directory 1998, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Product Directory, 1998; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: Union-Made Items Made by UNITE Members